{"country":[
	{"code":"AD","name":"Andorra","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":79218,"area":470,"points":4},
{"code":"AL","name":"Albania","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":2897366,"area":27400,"points":2},
{"code":"AT","name":"Austria","question":"why?","answer":"German","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":8479823,"area":82409,"points":5},
{"code":"AX","name":"Aland","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":28.007,"area":1580,"points":1},
{"code":"BA","name":"Bosnia and Herz.","question":"why?","answer":"Yes","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":3829307,"area":51000,"points":8},
{"code":"BE","name":"Belgium","question":"What's the name of a famous statue in Antwerp","answer":"Manneken Pis","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":11182817,"area":30280,"points":7},
{"code":"BG","name":"Bulgaria","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":7265115,"area":108560,"points":9},
{"code":"BY","name":"Belarus","question":"why?","answer":"Green","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":9466000,"area":202910,"points":6},
{"code":"CH","name":"Switzerland","question":"Why?","answer":"Bells","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":8087875,"area":39516,"points":59},
{"code":"CY","name":"Cyprus","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":1141166,"area":9240,"points":11},
{"code":"CZ","name":"Czech Rep.","question":"why?","answer":"Jagr","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":10514272,"area":77230,"points":12},
{"code":"DE","name":"Germany","question":"why?","answer":"Rammstein","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":80651873,"area":348540,"points":20},
{"code":"DK","name":"Denmark","question":"why?","answer":"Legos","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":5614932,"area":42430,"points":13},
{"code":"DZ","name":"Algeria","question":"why?","answer":"No","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":39208194,"area":2381740,"points":3},
{"code":"EE","name":"Estonia","question":"why?","answer":"Finland","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":1317997,"area":42390,"points":15},
{"code":"EG","name":"Egypt","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":82056378,"area":995450,"points":14},
{"code":"ES","name":"Spain","question":"why?","answer":"Matador","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":46617825,"area":498800,"points":57},
{"code":"FI","name":"Finland","question":"why?","answer":"Rovaniemi","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":5438972,"area":303890,"points":17},
{"code":"FO","name":"Faeroe Is.","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":49469,"area":1396,"points":16},
{"code":"FR","name":"France","question":"why?","answer":"Baguette","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":65939866,"area":547561,"points":18},
{"code":"GB","name":"United Kingdom","question":"why?","answer":"Chips","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":64106779,"area":241930,"points":64},
{"code":"GE","name":"Georgia","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":4487200,"area":69490,"points":19},
{"code":"GG","name":"Guernsey","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":null,"area":null,"points":22},
{"code":"GR","name":"Greece","question":"why?","answer":"Tzatziki","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":11027549,"area":128900,"points":21},
{"code":"HR","name":"Croatia","question":"why?","answer":"Banana split","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":4255700,"area":55960,"points":10},
{"code":"HU","name":"Hungary","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":9893899,"area":90530,"points":23},
{"code":"IE","name":"Ireland","question":"why?","answer":"Dublin","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":4597558,"area":68890,"points":26},
{"code":"IL","name":"Israel","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":8059500,"area":21640,"points":28},
{"code":"IM","name":"Isle of Man","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":85888,"area":570,"points":27},
{"code":"IQ","name":"Iraq","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":33417476,"area":434320,"points":25},
{"code":"IS","name":"Iceland","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":323764,"area":100250,"points":24},
{"code":"IT","name":"Italy","question":"why?","answer":"Gelato","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":60233948,"area":294140,"points":29},
{"code":"JE","name":"Jersey","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":99.500,"area":118,"points":30},
{"code":"LB","name":"Lebanon","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":4467390,"area":10230,"points":34},
{"code":"LI","name":"Liechtenstein","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":36925,"area":160,"points":36},
{"code":"LT","name":"Lithuania","question":"why?","answer":"Vilnius","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":2957689,"area":62674,"points":37},
{"code":"LU","name":"Luxembourg","question":"why?","answer":"Luxembourg","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":543360,"area":2590,"points":38},
{"code":"LV","name":"Latvia","question":"why?","answer":"Letts","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":2012647,"area":62180,"points":33},
{"code":"LY","name":"Libya","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":6201521,"area":1759540,"points":35},
{"code":"MA","name":"Morocco","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":33008150,"area":446300,"points":43},
{"code":"MD","name":"Moldova","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":3558566,"area":32860,"points":41},
{"code":"ME","name":"Montenegro","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":621383,"area":13450,"points":42},
{"code":"MK","name":"Macedonia","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":2107158,"area":25220,"points":39},
{"code":"MT","name":"Malta","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":423374,"area":180,"points":40},
{"code":"NCY","name":"N. Cyprus","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":3.355,"area":286257,"points":44},
{"code":"NL","name":"Netherlands","question":"why?","answer":"Tulips","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":16804432,"area":33720,"points":45},
{"code":"NO","name":"Norway","question":"why?","answer":"bergen","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":5080166,"area":365268,"points":46},
{"code":"PL","name":"Poland","question":"why?","answer":"Warsaw","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":38514479,"area":306220,"points":48},
{"code":"PS","name":"Palestine","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":null,"area":null,"points":47},
{"code":"PT","name":"Portugal","question":"why?","answer":"Cristiano Ronaldo","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":10457295,"area":91590,"points":49},
{"code":"RO","name":"Romania","question":"why?","answer":"Bulgaria","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":19981358,"area":230020,"points":50},
{"code":"RS","name":"Serbia","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":7164132,"area":87460,"points":54},
{"code":"RU","name":"Russia","question":"why?","answer":"Vladimir Putin","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":143499861,"area":16376870,"points":51},
{"code":"SA","name":"Saudi Arabia","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":28828870,"area":2149690,"points":53},
{"code":"SE","name":"Sweden","question":"why?","answer":"gustaf","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":9600379,"area":407340,"points":58},
{"code":"SI","name":"Slovenia","question":"why?","answer":"Croatia","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":2059953,"area":20140,"points":56},
{"code":"SK","name":"Slovakia","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":5413393,"area":48088,"points":55},
{"code":"SM","name":"San Marino","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":31448,"area":60,"points":52},
{"code":"SY","name":"Syria","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":22845550,"area":183630,"points":60},
{"code":"TN","name":"Tunisia","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":10886500,"area":155360,"points":61},
{"code":"TR","name":"Turkey","question":"why?","answer":"Istanbul","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":74932641,"area":769630,"points":62},
{"code":"UA","name":"Ukraine","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":45489600,"area":579320,"points":63},
{"code":"XK","name":"Kosovo","question":"why?","answer":".","answer-2":"Eifel tower","answer-3":"Christ the Redeemer","population":1824000,"area":10887,"points":32}
]}